A journey into iconic ‘90s horror.
In Search of Darkness: 1990-1994 is a documentary,
horror film directed by David A. Weiner.
Film icons and genre experts share observations, experiences, and analysis to help reframe,
deconstruct, and re-contextualize the "lost" decade of horror: the '90s.
Self, played by Mike Flanagan.
Self, played by David Dastmalchian.
Self, played by Clancy Brown.
Self, played by John Carpenter.
Self, played by Heather Langenkamp.
Self, played by Alex Winter.
In Search of Darkness is a 2019 documentary film
written and directed by David A.
Weiner and executive produced by Robin Block of CreatorVC Studios.
An international co-production of the United Kingdom and the United States, the film explores the development and lasting impact of the horror film genre during
the 1980s, and features interviews with numerous horror icons both from that decade and from the modern era, along with popular horror influencers.
In Search of Darkness premiered at the 2019 Beyond Fest.
The tone is dark.